http://www.carolinaraptorcenter.org/website-help/privacy-policy/

Website HelpPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Dumbledore, the Great Horned Owl, is watching! File Photo.About this imagePrivacy Policy
Carolina Raptor Center (CRC) values and respects indivduals’ privacy. It affirms that its fundraising, marketing and education practices protect against unauthorized use of its constituent lists. CRC will never sell or rent your personal information to other individuals or companies.
CRC utilizes ’ personal information such as names, mailing addresses and email addresses only for purposes of donor acknowledgement and/or when an individual voluntarily provides this information and opts to join our mailing list.
CRC does not share donors’ personal or contact information with any third party organizations for purposes of solicitation. However, it uses third-party vendors to facilitate the processing of donations made via credit card through www.carolinaraptorcenter.org. This third-party vendor complies with all security commerce guidelines and regulations to ensure the integrity and security of your information. CRC will never authorize vendors to sell or share your personal information.
For purposes of donor acknowledgement, CRC uses donor names, contact information and donation amounts for internal purposes only. It maintains appropriate security measures to keep this information private. CRC strives to ensure that all donors receive appropriate acknowledgment in an orderly, timely and effective manner.
Users can visit the website without revealing any information about themselves. However, information will be requested when making an online donation so that the gift may be properly processed and acknowledged. If users do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact, CRC will respect those wishes. All credit card transactions are conducted over a secure server and the credit card information is not retained or stored.
If you provide an email address or other personal information (excluding financial information) when you visit CRC’s website, this information may be entered into a data base for the purposes of contacting you in the future to ask your input, provide information about programs and events, and request contributions. If you would like to withhold your information from such an exchange, you can opt out of receiving email messages from CRC as a link included in all of our email communications.
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures and tools to safeguard and secure the information we collect. We treat data as an asset that must be protected at all costs. We employ many different security techniques to protect against loss and unauthorized access.
CRC’s website automatically records information about your visit in server logs. This information is not personally identifiable. This data is analyzed for trends, insights and statistics. For example, it may show how many people visited the website during a certain time period. We use a number of web analytics products to optimize our website, including Google Analytics. These tools do not require our site visitors to identify themselves, and they do not provide us any personally identifiable information about our visitors that is not supplied voluntarily. Our goal in using analytics is to understand what parts of our website you like and which parts need work.
CRC welcomes comments and questions about this policy. It is committed to protecting your personal information, and will make every reasonable effort to keep that information secure. CRC reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time and will post the changes on this web page.
Connect to our Institutional Financials.
Check us out on Guidestar.
For other questions, please contact Kris Cole, Director of Marketing & Development at kcole@carolinaraptorcenter.org or (704) 875-8521 x204.
* Entrance closes 30 minutes before the end of the session.
